Correspondence from the Elizabeth Sprague Coolidge Foundation Collection
Music Division, Library of Congress
- Correspondence, 1894-1953 (Box 1-109)
  - Washington Music Teachers' Association (Washington, D.C.) (Box-folder 102/44)
  - Washington, D.C. National Woman's Country Club (Box-folder 102/45)
  - Washington, D.C. newspapers (Box-folder 102/46)
  - Washington D.C. Public Library see District of Columbia. Public Library
  - Washington D.C. Security Storage Company (Box-folder 102/47)
  - Washington D.C. Women's National Press Club (U.S.) (Box-folder 102/48)
  - Washington D.C. miscellany (Box-folder 102/49)
  - Washington Square (N.Y.) Association (Box-folder 102/50)
  - Washington (State) University (Box-folder 102/51)
  - "Wat-Way" miscellaneous see also "W" miscellaneous (Box-folder 103/1)
  - Waters, Edward N. see Library of Congress. Waters, Edward N.
  - Wathen, Lawrence James (Box-folder 103/2)
  - Watson, Dorothy De Muth (Box-folder 103/3)
  - Watson, Gertrude, 1921-1925 (Box-folder 103/4)
  - Watson, Gertrude, 1926-1929 (Box-folder 103/5)
  - Watson, Gertrude, 1930-1932 (Box-folder 103/6)
  - Watson, Gertrude, 1933-1934 (Box-folder 103/7)
  - Watson, Gertrude, 1935-1938 (Box-folder 103/8)
  - Watson, Gertrude, undated (Box-folder 103/9)
  - Watts, Wintter (Box-folder 103/10)
  - Watumull, G. J. (Box-folder 103/11)
  - Wayman, Willard Ormsby, Mrs. (Box-folder 103/12)
  - "We" miscellaneous see also "W" miscellaneous (Box-folder 103/13)
  - Weaver, Lawrence G. see Paravox Hearing Aids
  - Webb, Jessie S. (Box-folder 103/14)
  - Webber, Charlotte (Box-folder 103/15)
  - Webern, Anton (Box-folder 103/16)
  - Weigl, Karl and Vally (Box-folder 103/17)
  - Weill, Julie (Box-folder 103/18)
  - Weiner, Leó (Box-folder 103/19)
  - Weinrich, Carl (Box-folder 103/20)
  - Weinstock, Herbert H. (Box-folder 103/21)
  - Weinstock, Rachmael H. (Box-folder 103/22)
  - Weisbach, Harry (Box-folder 103/23)
  - Weiss, Adolph (Box-folder 103/24)
  - Weisshaus, Imre (Box-folder 103/25)
  - Welch, Archibald A. (Box-folder 103/26)
  - Welch, Roy Dickinson see Smith College. Welch, Roy Dickinson and Princeton University. Welch, Roy Dickinson
  - Wellesley College. Hamilton, Clarence G. (Box-folder 103/27)
  - Wellesley College. Hinners, Howard (Box-folder 103/28)
  - Wellesley College. LaRue, Jan (Box-folder 103/29)
  - Wellesley College. McAfee, Mildred H. (Box-folder 103/30)
  - Wellesley College. MacDougall, Hamilton C. (Box-folder 103/31)
  - Wellesley College. McManus, Lillian Whitney (Box-folder 103/32)
  - Wellesley College. Pendleton, Ellen (Box-folder 103/33)
  - Wellesley College miscellany (Box-folder 103/34)
  - Wellesz, Egon (Box-folder 103/35)
  - Wells College (Box-folder 103/36)
  - "Wen" miscellaneous see also "W" miscellaneous (Box-folder 104/1)
  - Wendling, Carl (Box-folder 104/2)
  - Wentworth, Frank W. see Mills College
  - Wentworth, Jean P. see Mills College
  - Werfel, Alma Mahler (Box-folder 104/3)
  - Werrenrath, Reinald (Box-folder 104/4)
  - Wertheim, Alma (Box-folder 104/5)
  - Wesleyan University (Middletown, Conn.) (Box-folder 104/6)
  - Wessel, Mark (Box-folder 104/7)
  - Wessels, Frederick J. and Minnie, 1916-1926 (Box-folder 105/1)
  - Wessels, Frederick J. and Minnie, 1932-1933 (Box-folder 105/2)
  - Wessels, Frederick J. and Minnie, 1934 (Box-folder 105/3)
  - Wessels, Frederick J. and Minnie, 1935 (Box-folder 105/4)
  - Wessels, Frederick J. and Minnie, 1936 (Box-folder 105/5)
  - Wessels, Frederick J. and Minnie, 1937 (Box-folder 105/6)
  - Wessels, Frederick J. and Minnie, 1938 January-June (Box-folder 105/7)
  - Wessels, Frederick J. and Minnie, 1938 July-December (Box-folder 105/8)
  - Wessels, Frederick J. and Minnie, 1939 January-May (Box-folder 105/9)
  - Wessels, Frederick J. and Minnie, 1939 July-December (Box-folder 105/10)
  - Wessels, Frederick J. and Minnie, 1940 January-June (Box-folder 105/11)
  - Wessels, Frederick J. and Minnie, 1940 July-December (Box-folder 105/12)
  - Wessels, Frederick J. and Minnie, 1941 (Box-folder 105/13)
  - Wessels, Frederick J. and Minnie, 1942 (Box-folder 105/14)
  - Wessels, Frederick J. and Minnie, 1943 (Box-folder 105/15)
  - Wessels, Frederick J. and Minnie, 1944-1945 (Box-folder 105/16)
  - Wessels, Frederick J. and Minnie, 1946-1947 (Box-folder 105/17)
  - Wessels, Frederick J. and Minnie, 1948-1949 (Box-folder 105/18)
  - Wessels, Frederick J. and Minnie, post 1936, Contains undated letters on "Up-A-Long Hill Road" stationery. (Box-folder 105/19)
  - Wessels, Frederick J. and Minnie, undated, Contains letters on miscellaneous stationery. (Box-folder 105/20)
  - Wessels, Frederick J. and Minnie, undated, Contains greeting cards and calling cards. (Box-folder 105/21)
  - West, Birnie (Mrs. Frank West) (Box-folder 104/8)
  - Western Union (Box-folder 104/9)
  - Westminster Choir College see also Williamson, John Finley (Box-folder 104/10)
  - Weston, Karl E. (Box-folder 104/11)
  - "Wh" miscellaneous see also "W" miscellaneous (Box-folder 104/12)
  - Wheeler, Robert C. (Box-folder 104/13)
  - "Whit-Whu" miscellaneous see also "W" miscellaneous (Box-folder 104/14)
  - White, Clarence Cameron (Box-folder 104/15)
  - White, Eric Walter (Box-folder 104/16)
  - White, Felix (Box-folder 104/17)
  - White, Lynn see Mills College. White, Lynn
  - Whitehead, John B. and Mrs. (Box-folder 104/18)
  - Whitehouse, Henry Howard, Mrs. (Box-folder 104/19)
  - Whithorne, Emerson (Box-folder 104/20)
  - Whiting, Arthur and Grace, 1922-1926 (Box-folder 104/21)
  - Whiting, Arthur and Grace, 1927-1934, undated (Box-folder 104/22)
  - Whitman College (Box-folder 104/23)
  - Whitney, L. Annie (Box-folder 104/25)
  - Whitney, Marylou (Mrs. Cornelius Vanderbilt Whitney) (Box-folder 104/24)
  - Whitney, Robert S. (Box-folder 104/26)
  - Whittaker, William Gillies (Box-folder 104/27)
  - Whittall, Gertrude Clarke (Box-folder 104/28)
  - "Wi" miscellaneous see also "W" miscellaneous (Box-folder 104/29)
  - Wiborg, Mary Hoyt (Box-folder 104/30)
  - Wickerham, Mary see Mid-West Music Foundation
  - Wickman, Frank (Box-folder 104/31)
  - Wien. Gesellschaft der Musikfreunde see Vienna. Gesellschaft der Musikfreunde
  - Wiener, Paul, Mrs. see Wertheim, Alma
  - Wigglesworth, Frank Jr., Frank Sr., Annie, and "Bay" (Box-folder 104/32)
  - "Wil" miscellaneous see also "W" miscellaneous (Box-folder 104/33)
  - Wilbur, Ray Lyman see Stanford University. Wilbur, Ray Lyman
  - Wilkins, Henry Blakiston, Emily Howell Wilkins, and Alice Garrett Wilkins (Box-folder 104/34)
  - "Will-Wilm" miscellaneous see also "W" miscellaneous (Box-folder 106/1)
  - Willeke, Willem, 1917-1919 (Box-folder 107/1)
  - Willeke, Willem, 1920-1921 (Box-folder 107/2)
  - Willeke, Willem, 1922-1923 (Box-folder 107/3)
  - Willeke, Willem, 1924 (Box-folder 107/4)
  - Willeke, Willem, 1925-1926 (Box-folder 107/5)
  - Willeke, Willem, 1927 (Box-folder 107/6)
  - Willeke, Willem, 1928-1929 (Box-folder 107/7)
  - Willeke, Willem, 1930-1931 (Box-folder 107/8)
  - Willeke, Willem, 1932-1933 (Box-folder 107/9)
  - Willeke, Willem, 1934 (Box-folder 107/10)
  - Willeke, Willem, 1935 (Box-folder 107/11)
  - Willeke, Willem, 1936 (Box-folder 107/12)
  - Willeke, Willem, 1937 (Box-folder 107/13)
  - Willeke, Willem, 1938-1939 (Box-folder 107/14)
  - Willeke, Willem, 1940-1941 (Box-folder 107/15)
  - Willeke, Willem, 1942-1945 (Box-folder 107/16)
  - Willeke, Willem, 1946-1948 (Box-folder 107/17)
  - Willeke, Willem, 1949 (Box-folder 107/18)
  - Willeke, Willem, 1950 (Box-folder 107/19)
  - Willeke, Sally (Mrs. Willem Willeke), 1951 (Box-folder 107/20)
  - Willeke, Sally (Mrs. Willem Willeke), 1952 (Box-folder 107/21)
  - Willeke, Sally (Mrs. Willem Willeke), 1953 (Box-folder 107/22)
  - Willeke, Willem, undated (presumed early) (Box-folder 107/23)
  - Willeke, Willem, undated (presumed 1921-1933) (Box-folder 107/24)
  - Willeke, Willem, undated (Box-folder 107/25)
  - Williams, Lewis (Box-folder 106/2)
  - Williams College see also Nin-Culmell, Joaquín
  - Williams College. Barrow, R. G. (Box-folder 106/3)
  - Williams College. Baxter, James P. (Box-folder 106/4)
  - Williams College. Garfield, H. W. (Box-folder 106/5)
  - Williams College. Safford, Charles L. and Laura (Box-folder 106/6)
  - Williams College. Miscellany (Box-folder 106/7)
  - Williamsburg see Colonial Williamsburg
  - Williamson, John Finley see also Westminster Choir College (Box-folder 106/8)
  - Willis, Lyle L. (Box-folder 106/9)
  - Wilmann, Allan (Box-folder 106/10)
  - "Wils" miscellaneous see also "W" miscellaneous (Box-folder 106/11)
  - Wilson, Edith Bolling (Mrs. Woodrow Wilson) (Box-folder 106/12)
  - Wilson, Edmund B. and Anne Kidder Wilson (Box-folder 106/13)
  - Wilson, Steuart (Box-folder 106/14)
  - Wilstach, Paul (Box-folder 106/15)
  - "Win" miscellaneous see also "W" miscellaneous (Box-folder 106/16)
  - Wind Instrument Ensemble of San Francisco (Box-folder 106/17)
  - Winetzkaja, Maria (Box-folder 106/18)
  - Winfield, Kansas. Public Schools (Box-folder 106/19)
  - Winkler, Emil K. see Wells College
  - Winship, Laurence L. ("Larry") and Ruth (Box-folder 106/20)
  - Winship, Thomas and Elizabeth see also Coolidge, Elizabeth (granddaughter) (Box-folder 106/21)
  - Winslow, Bertha Russell (Mrs. Samuel E. Winslow) (Box-folder 106/22)
  - Winslow, Harriet (Box-folder 106/23)
  - Winternitz, Felix (Box-folder 106/24)
  - Wirths, Edmond (Box-folder 106/25)
  - "Wis-Wit" miscellaneous see also "W" miscellaneous (Box-folder 106/26)
  - Wisconsin. University see also Johansen, Gunnar
  - Wisconsin. University. Bricken, Carl, 1936-1939 (Box-folder 106/27)
  - Wisconsin. University. Bricken, Carl, 1940 (Box-folder 106/28)
  - Wisconsin. University. Bricken, Carl, 1941 (Box-folder 106/29)
  - Wisconsin. University. Bricken, Carl, 1942-1944 (Box-folder 106/30)
  - Wisconsin. University. Bricken, Carl, undated (Box-folder 106/31)
  - Wisconsin. University. Miscellany (Box-folder 106/32)
  - Wister, Frances A. see Philadelphia Orchestra
  - Wit, Gertrude Marshall (Box-folder 106/33)
  - Witherspoon, Herbert and Florence Hinkle (Box-folder 106/34)
  - Withington, Alfreda B. (Box-folder 106/35)
  - "Wo" miscellaneous see also "W" miscellaneous (Box-folder 108/1)
  - Woelber, Frank (Box-folder 108/2)
  - Wolfinsohn, Wolfe and Sally, 1923-1945 (Box-folder 108/3)
  - Wolfinsohn, Wolfe and Sally, 1946-1949 (Box-folder 108/4)
  - Wolfinsohn, Wolfe and Sally, 1950-1953 (Box-folder 108/5)
  - Wolfinsohn, Wolfe and Sally, undated (Box-folder 108/6)
  - Wolfsohn Musical Bureau (Box-folder 108/7)
  - Wolle, John Frederick (Box-folder 108/8)
  - Wood, Annabelle (Box-folder 108/9)
  - Wood, Henry (Box-folder 108/10)
  - Wood, J. Henry (Box-folder 108/11)
  - Wood, Nathaniel K. (Box-folder 108/12)
  - Wood, P. K. (Box-folder 108/13)
  - Wood Hill, Mabel, 1933-1939 (Box-folder 108/14)
  - Wood Hill, Mabel, 1940-1951 (Box-folder 108/15)
  - Wood Hill, Mabel, undated (Box-folder 108/16)
  - Woodson, Mary Kay (Box-folder 108/17)
  - Woodworth, G. Wallace see Harvard University. Woodworth, G. Wallace
  - Woodworth, Mabel see Southern California. University
  - Woollett, Henry (Box-folder 108/18)
  - Woollett, Wilfred (Box-folder 108/19)
  - Woolley, Mary E. see Mount Holyoke College
  - Workers' Defense League (Box-folder 108/20)
  - World Republic (Box-folder 108/21)
  - World Wide Broadcasting Foundation (Box-folder 108/22)
  - Worswick, Mildred see Stanford University. Mears, Eliot G.
  - Woytych, Helen (Box-folder 108/23)
  - "Wr" miscellaneous see also "W" miscellaneous (Box-folder 108/24)
  - Wright, Helen (Mrs. Charles Wright), 1917-1938 (Box-folder 108/25)
  - Wright, Helen (Mrs. Charles Wright), 1942-1949 (Box-folder 108/26)
  - Wright, Helen (Mrs. Charles Wright), 1950-1951 (Box-folder 108/27)
  - Wright, Helen (Mrs. Charles Wright), 1952-1953 (Box-folder 108/28)
  - Wright, Helen (Mrs. Charles Wright), undated (Box-folder 108/29)
  - Wurlitzer, Rudolph H. (Box-folder 108/30)
  - Wyatt, Edith Franklin (Box-folder 108/31)
  - Wyman, Loraine (Box-folder 108/32)
  - Wyschnegradsky, Ivan, Mrs. (Box-folder 108/33)
  - Mrs. Coolidge's "W" "see" references (Box-folder 108/34)
  - "W" not identified (Box-folder 108/35)
  - "Y" miscellaneous (Box-folder 109/1)
  - Yaddo see Ames, Elizabeth
  - Yale University see also Smith, David Stanley and Parker, Horatio
  - Yale University endowment, establishment of Sprague Hall, 1915 (Box-folder 109/2)
  - Yale University. Simonds, Bruce (Box-folder 109/3)
  - Yale University: miscellaneous letters (Box-folder 109/4)
  - Yale University: miscellaneous non-correspondence (Box-folder 109/5)
  - Yarros, Victor S. (Box-folder 109/6)
  - Yeomans, Julia (Box-folder 109/7)
  - Yost, Gaylord (Box-folder 109/8)
  - Young, Josephine E. (Mrs. Owen D. Young) (Box-folder 109/9)
  - Young, Leonore O. see San Mateo. Country Concert Association
  - Young Men's Christian Associaton (Box-folder 109/10)
  - Young Men's Hebrew Association (Box-folder 109/11)
  - Young Women's Christian Association (Box-folder 109/12)
  - "Z" miscellaneous (Box-folder 109/13)
  - Zach, Max (Box-folder 109/14)
  - Zádor, Eugene (Box-folder 109/15)
  - Zam, Maurice (Box-folder 109/16)
  - Zanco, Eugénie de (Box-folder 109/17)
  - Zeisler, Fannie Bloomfield (Box-folder 109/18)
  - Zetlin, Emanuel (Box-folder 109/19)
  - Ziehn, Bernhard (Box-folder 109/20)
  - Zighera, Alfred (Box-folder 109/21)
  - Zighera, Bernard (Box-folder 109/22)
  - Zimbalist, Alma Gluck see Gluck, Alma
  - Zimbalist, Efrem (Box-folder 109/23)
  - Zimbalist, Mary Louise Curtis Bok see Bok, Mary Louise Curtis
  - Zimbler, Josef, 1945-1950 (Box-folder 109/24)
  - Zimbler, Josef, 1951-1952 (Box-folder 109/25)
  - Zimbler, Josef, undated (Box-folder 109/26)